look everybody and their dog knows my sequel it's
free and open source so it's easy to start with
but it's not so easy once your data really starts
to scale mysql is fast for a relational database
but at scale responses get really slow
and if i'm running secondary indexes
forget it do you know of anyone running their
high performance applications off of my sql
no they are subsetting data from my sql to some
other performance solution well i can think of a
performance solution redis enterprise the
world's leading real-time data platform
redis enterprise can be used alongside your mysql
database to store your application's most critical
and commonly access data in memory to deliver it
with sub millisecond speed what about those pesky
secondary indexed queries you can use redis
enterprise to offload them which speeds up
the responses to your applications and takes some
of that skilling pain off of your mysql database
mind blown check out the webinar below to learn
more and see my sql and redis enterprise in action